let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
    answer: "All of the above.",
    options: [
      "JavaScript is a lightweight, interpreted programming language",
      "JavaScript is designed for creating network-centric applications",
      "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java.",
      "All of the above."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the most used programming language in 2019?",
    answer: "Javascript",
    options: [
      "java",
      "C",
      "Python",
      "Javascript"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which year was JavaScript launched?",
    answer: 1995,
    options: [
      1996,
      1995,
      1994,
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

{
    numb: 4,
    question: "What does HTML stand for?",
    answer:"Hypertext Markup Language",
    options: [
        "Hypertext Markup Language",
        "Cascading Style Sheet",
        "Jason Object Notation",
        "Helicopters Terminals Motorboats Lamborginis",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
    answer: "Object-oriented",
    options: [
          "Object-oriented",
          "Object-based",
          "Procedural",
          "None of the above",
      ]
    },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " Which of the following code creates an object?",
    answer: "var book = new Object();",
    options: [
        "var book = Object();",
        "var book = new Object();" ,
        "var book = new OBJECT();",
        "var book = new Book();",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " Which of the following code creates an objWhich of the following function of Boolean object returns a string containing the source of the Boolean object?",
    answer: "toSource()",
    options: [
         "toSource()",
         "valueOf()",
         "toString()",
         "None of the above.",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " Which of the following function of String object returns a string representing the specified object?",
    answer: "toString()",
    options: [
        "toLocaleUpperCase()",
        "toUpperCase()" ,
        "toString()",
        "substring()",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "  Which of the following function of Array object joins all elements of an array into a string?",
    answer: "join()",
    options: [
        "concat()",
        "join()" ,
        "pop()",
        "map()",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
        "var",
        "let" ,
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the above",
    ]
  },
]


